http://www.mgownersclub.co.uk/terms-and-conditions

Jump to navigation
You are hereHome › Club Matters ›
Terms and Conditions
Welcome to our website. If you continue to browse and use this website, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the following terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern MGOC Ltd t/a MG Owners’ Club relationship with you in relation to this website. If you disagree with any part of these terms and conditions, please do not use our website.
The term 'MG Owners’ Club' or 'us' or 'we' refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is M G O C Limited, Stirling House, 165-175 Farnham Road, Slough, Berkshire, SL1 4UZ.
Our company registration number is registered in London under Company number 1204646. MGOC Limited trades as MG Owners’ Club. The term 'you' refers to the user or viewer of our website. The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use: co.uk
The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.
Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. You acknowledge that such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.
Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, for which we shall not be liable. It shall be your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.
This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.
All trade marks reproduced in this website which are not the property of, or licensed to, the operator are acknowledged on the website.
Unauthorised use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence.
From time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).
Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of England, Northern Ireland, Scotland and Wales.
If you choose, or you are provided with, a user identification code, password or any other piece of information as part of our security procedures, you must treat such information as confidential and you must not disclose it to any third party.  We have the right to disable any user identification code or password, whether chosen by you or allocated by us, at any time, if in our opinion you have failed to comply with any of the provisions of these terms.  By using the website you acknowledge that you are responsible for making all arrangements necessary for you to have access to the website.  You are also responsible for ensuring that all persons who access the website through your internet connection are aware of these terms and they comply with them.
User generated content Your user content means material (including without limitation text, images, audio material, video material and audio-visual material) that you submit to our website, for whatever purpose. You grant to us a worldwide, irrevocable, non-exclusive, royalty-free licence to use, reproduce, adapt, publish, translate and distribute your user content in any existing or future media. You also grant to us the right to sub-license these rights, and the right to bring an action for infringement of these rights. Your user content must not be illegal or unlawful, must not infringe any third party's legal rights, and must not be capable of giving rise to legal action whether against you or us or a third party (in each case under any applicable law). You must not submit any user content to the website that is or has ever been the subject of any threatened or actual legal proceedings or other similar complaint. We reserve the right to edit or remove any material submitted to our website, or stored on our servers, or hosted or published upon our website. Notwithstanding our rights under these terms and conditions in relation to user content, we do not undertake to monitor the submission of such content to, or the publication of such content on, our website.  Links to other websites Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at membercare@mgownerslub.co.uk
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about our services. For further information please read our privacy policy
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to us or complete the members contact us form as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Subscription Refund  Policy Refunds are calculated based on the number of magazines that have been received during the 12 months subscription. If there are 3 issues or less that remain then no refund will be made. Refunds will be made by transfer to your Bank Account (if we hold these details) or by cheque. All refunds will incur an administration fee of £5. Cancellation and Return Policy If you are not totally satisfied with your membership welcome pack and any aspect of the services that we offer, please return your complete welcome pack and membership card with your reasons for cancellation within 14 days from the date of application. We will apply a full refund to either your credit card or by transfer to your Bank Account depending on which method was used for the initial payment. Membership Pack Delivery Policy Please allow up to 7 working days in the UK and up to 14 days to outside the UK for your membership card and welcome pack to be delivered. Gift Membership Delivery Policy Please allow up to 7 working days in the UK and up to 14 days to outside the UK for your Gift Membership to be delivered to your recipient.
Website disclaimer The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by the MG Owners’ Club and while we endeavour to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.
In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.
Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However, the MG Owners’ Club takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.Copyright notice
This website and its content are copyright of the MG Owners’ Club - © MGOC Ltd. All rights reserved. Any redistribution or reproduction of part or all of the contents in any form is prohibited other than the following:
you may print or download to a local hard disk extracts for your personal and non-commercial use only
you may copy the content to individual third parties for their personal use, but only if you acknowledge the website as the source of the material
You may not, except with our express written permission, distribute or commercially exploit the content. Nor may you transmit it or store it in any other website or other form of electronic retrieval system.
Home
Club MattersAbout Us
Affiliated Clubs
Benefits
Contact us
Downloads
FAQ
Feedback
